Hi, my name is Bobby Charalambos. I live here in the area for the last 45 years.
But unfortunately, my first accident, I ended up looking for reviews online.
I found this place. They had great reviews.
I came in, I talked to Ed and Eddie Jr.
and we kicked it off right off the bat.
Real personable. These guys are like family to me now.
I have a vehicle that's very rare. There's only 200 made.
It's a Lexus GS 350 Black Line. So I was between going
to shops in Illinois and so forth. I ended up finding this place,
read the reviews, came in and spoke with them, and right away, I just felt
comfortable dealing with Ed and Eddie Jr.
From start to finish, they updated me
with every single process, what was going on, when parts were coming, when the
vehicle was going to be done. At the end of the day, the vehicle was done three
days earlier, and they brought their painter, Ivan,
in, showed me exactly what was done.
I couldn't be happier. Since then, unfortunately, I've had two
vehicles here for other body work, and I couldn't be
happier. I've had work done at other body shops here in Cherry Hill.
Big difference, though, huh?
The work is phenomenal. I couldn't be happier.
And now-
Knock on wood.
... I don't have no vehicles to bring in, but I stop by and I see Ed and Eddie
because these guys, again, they're like family.